### İletişim Bilgileri

2005.tolgahan+linkedin@gmai l.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tolgahan-acar (LinkedIn)

tolgahanacar.net (Personal)

# En Önemli Yetenekler PHP

MySQL

React.js

### Languages

Türkçe (Native or Bilingual) İngilizce (Professional Working)

#### Certifications

Java (Basic)
Digital Marketing
Blockchain

# Tolgahan Acar

Software Developer

İstanbul

## Özet

I have 3-4 years of full-time I.T work experience in corporate companies. As a software developer, I did not work full time in a company, but I have 2-3 years of experience as a freelancer. I work with a back-end focus, but I do not hesitate to work full-stack. Technologies I Use

Nodejs / Expressjs, PHP / Laravel, Javascript / Reactjs / JQuery / ES6, SQL / NoSQL, CSS / Tailwindcss/ Bootstrap, Python / Django, SEO

- Clean Code
- Design Pattern
- Secure Code

## Deneyim

İstanbul Esnaf ve Sanatkarlar Odaları Birliği 2 yıl 11 ay

Information Technology Staff Ekim 2018 - Present (2 yıl 11 ay) Istanbul, Turkey

ISO Quality Representative Kasım 2020 - Present (10 ay)

Istanbul, Turkey

tolgahanacar.net Founder Ağustos 2019 - Present (2 yıl 1 ay) Istanbul, Turkey

Imgelem Creative Agency
IT Company Representative

Ekim 2018 - Ocak 2020 (1 yıl 4 ay)

Istanbul, Turkey

İstanbul Esnaf ve Sanatkarlar Odaları Birliği Information Technology Intern Eylül 2017 - Haziran 2018 (10 ay)

# **Eğitim**

İstanbul Gelişim Üniversitesi ÖnLisans, Bilgisayar Programlama/Programcı, Genel · (2018 - 2020)